datingpro.com 2006-12-27

# Pilot Group - Privacy and Security

**Information Collection & Use** _Registration_  
In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information such as name and email address. We use this information to contact you on site services you have expressed interest in.

Pilot Group LTD is the sole owner of the information collected on www.pilotgroup.net . Your privacy is of high importance to us and we do everything possible to protect any information you provide us.

Our policies are created to maximize your enjoyment and benefit. Pilot Group Ltd values the privacy of all site visitors and customers and does not provide individually identifiable information to third parties.

Pilot Group LTD collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. If a customer chooses to provide personally identifiable information to Pilot Group Ltd by making a purchase, faxing information, requesting additional information through email or telephone, or communicating directly with Pilot Group Ltd, this information remains secure and will not be used for anything other than the purpose for which it was obtained.

We do not share, rent, sell or otherwise distribute customer information with other persons, companies, affiliates or organizations.

 _Orders_  
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. To process an order made on our site, we require information such as your name, billing address, phone number, email address, shipping address and credit card information. This information is relayed to us via our shopping cart service and at our payment gateway billing page.

It is used to process your order and possibly contact you by phone or email. This information, and only that information which is absolutely necessary, will be shared with those third parties that are involved in the processing, filling, and shipping of your order. For example: payment gateway you used for order processing.

Pilot Group Ltd may also collect your computer's IP address. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, administer and market our Web site, and track fraudulent credit card transactions. Your IP address is used to help identify you and may be used to gather broad demographic information. No personal information about you (i.e., your name, email address, etc.) is gathered or collected from your IP address. We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

During installation, customization and integration work we can use your access data to your ftp and to your hosting control panel. We do not use this information for any other purposes and do not share them with third party companies.

For security measures we would advise our clients to change ftp server information and admin mode access codes after the work on their site is finished. This guarantees our clients confidence and security of their personal information. We can request this information again if any fixes or new functions are needed.

This site has strict security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. All information is stored on secure servers and stringent policies govern the use and handling of such information.

 _Application Forms_  
If you apply for several contact forms or service requiring financial information on our site, we require that you provide certain personally identifiable information, including your name and email address. This information is necessary to process your application and to contact you. _Surveys_  
We may provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information, such as name and email address.

We use this information to personalize the site and to get any suggestions for improvement of our products, services and our site, to notify our clients of the possible changes by Pilot Group LTD newsletter.

Information users submit is used by the site to create a list of customers, to generate discounts and notifications for users, to subscribe or unsubscribe users to our newsletter service, to identify request, application, free installation, instant callback, complaint, contact via online and suggestion forms.

**Communications from the Site**

 _Special Offers and Updates_  
We will occasionally send you information on our products, services, special deals, promotions and updates. You can sign up for these emails on our home page.

You can subscribe or unsubscribe to Pilot Group LTD newsletter. If you wish to do it we will use your name and email address to send this kind of information to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.

 _Customer Service_  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email, live chat or phone, in accordance with your wishes _Profile_  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs to be able to contact our clients if need arises. We do not share your profile with other third parties.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources. We use some third party sources when checking the data our users provide us with, such as ID Verification. We use THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE to verify your address, in order to avoid cases of fraud.

We do not share aggregated information about our user base with our partners and advertisers.

**Log files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data.  
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site and to track users' movements around the site. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of PilotGroup.net Web Site you have visited, personalized or customized, so the next time you visit those pages may be readily accessible.  
You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to notify you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites will not work as intended.

We use session ID cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.  
If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.pilotgroup.net only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**

We employ a software technology called clear gifs, that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information.

**Links to Other Sites**

This web site may contain links to other sites. Pilot Group Ltd is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. Pilot Group Ltd does not share any of the individual personal information you provide to us with the Web sites to which Pilot Group Ltd links. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  
This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing our Customer Support at support@pilotgroup.net or by contacting us by telephone, live chat or email.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**Contact Us**

Should you have some questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement or the practices of this site, contact Pilot Group Support or Sales Team by [online contact form](http://www.pilotgroup.net/support/), via Live Chat at any of our site or via phone number 1-888-228-8440 (toll free line).
